hi welcome back to the body to the class
and we're going to continue with this
cool things that will happen to you
if you can get to bully china if you can
have this experience of jumping
from planet to planet and
you know if you live in new york city
and i lived in new york city for a long
time
uh you know during the time i was
building the diamond business
uh you know people who live in new york
never go to the famous places in new
york like i live near the grand canyon
for 12 15 years and i've never been
there
and uh you know people in new york they
never
i never been to the statue of liberty uh
you know it's the most famous place and
then
people would ask me when the world trade
center was
there my brother came to visit me
from arizona and he said take me to the
highest building you know and i said
okay
i has i've never been there myself i'd
like to
see it you know so we went to the world
trade center
and we got up to the top
and something happened while i was up
there
and it was very very strange the whole
building went like this
the whole building went like like moved
sideways
very noticeably and i actually thought
it was falling down or something
i got very secure and the whole building
went like this
and um then i told my brother you know i
gotta go
i i can't stay up here and uh he said
are you okay and i said i don't know i
just felt the whole building
moved like this you know and and
skyscrapers do move a little bit
but it was different it was uh it was
like the whole building was gonna fall
down
and i said i gotta get out of here and
and we went down
and um and that's called in tibetan
there's a special word for that it's
called
sayo
like hey yo it's like goes like this you
know
why are we talking about that uh the
text if we go to the text now
it says chang jiu ji sim k if
one person in the universe
gets to bodhichitta real bully chin if
they jump
start jumping between planet sayo
you can see it there sayo means the
whole
earth goes the the
the earth and all the buddha paradise is
going
they move like this you know like an
earthquake you know
and uh
even the thrones the teaching thrones
that all the buddhas are sitting on
medicine buddha also sitting on a throne
right
and then if one person in the whole
universe
gets bodhichitted that day then the
buddha's
seed also goes medicine is like whoa
what's going on
and uh they say oh somebody got buddy
today wow
cool you know and uh
pablo mache being a geshe
he asked why why
why does the earth move you know when
someone gets bony tuna
and by the way i have a picture here
that i really enjoy
uh this is a very famous picture in the
united states
it was taken about
about 80 years ago or something and
these guys are
sitting on a piece of steel when they're
building
those first big high buildings in in new
york and this is a real picture they
were
i think it was rockefeller center and
they were about 800 feet up
and they were all having lunch on the on
the girder
and i'm just hoping no one gets
bodhichitta at the moment
because it would go like that you know
so uh
maybe that picture will help you
remember
why why does the universe
suddenly move and he answers his
question
denis said sad chambody if you think
about it
the earth that we're all sitting on even
in the buddha paradise
two the earth that we're sitting on
wherever we're sitting even the buddha
is created by the shared karma
of all the people in the universe all
the places where
people are sitting right now you are
listening to this program
from different countries but the the
the ground that you're sitting on even
the buddhas in their buddha paranoia
all that ground has been created by the
shared karma of all of us we are partly
responsible
for the earth in the buddha paradises
because it exists in our universe so you
and i have
partly i mean medicine buddha should be
paying rent to us
because we all help create
that universe that's a common
a shared karma and people ask me you
know
of course you know the answer is it
possible for
two people to create a karma together
and sure
if you all decide to have a to work hard
tim and his team work very hard
to organize a special dharma event
around the world then all the people on
that team
all the translators all the tech people
all the people who drove me here
yesterday with all my stuff uh
we're all creating a karma together so
the world
the universe is a shared karma
the ground that all beings are sitting
on
is a shared karma okay he says
[Music]
and the whole point
of bodhichitta is the desire
to help countless beings on countless
planets
who have also created those planets
so when you have the intention
to help all those beings sitting on all
those planets
the planets that you created for those
beings
have to move it's very beautiful it's
very
your karma personally
when you get body china is
linked to the ground everywhere
so it has to move and then he says uh
it's too heavy for the ground not to
move
okay the ground can't support
uh 10 minutes of bodhichitta
the ground of the whole universe is
is holding up everybody in the universe
and normally it's okay you know i can do
it
i can hold up everybody in the universe
i don't have to move you know
but oh somebody just got put each other
ass too heavy
and the ground has to you know the
ground shakes because it's like you
added
100 pounds to somebody's backpack and
then they're like oh
so it's such a powerful karma
when someone jumps planet
uh to to meet each being and and commit
to their happiness
uh that the earth cannot bear it okay
literally cannot bear it the word bear
comes from bir
in sanskrit which means to to hold up
something
burden comes from that
bertha comes from that which is that's a
long story
all right um
each person who is able to jump
planets is considered also
a brother or sister by the other
bodhisattvas who are already
there so they're like obviously the
buddhists are super happy
because they got new kids in the family
and it's not that they love you more
than anybody else
it's it's not that you know they're
going to love you more because you're in
the family
and they don't love you if you're not in
the family they love everybody equally
but they especially love you
they especially equally love you okay
and the other body suffers in the
universe i'm like
hey i got a new brother i got a new
sister
it's like you got married when i got
married i got four extra sisters
you know i never had a sister so it's
like really cool
and i feel happy you know i feel happy
to call someone's sister
you know and so all these bodhisattvas
are so happy
so there's a big thing uh okay i did
watch netflix recently i was watching
alexander the great story because it's
connected to the silk road in india and
one of alexander's big problems in his
life was he never had a son
or he was trying to have a son and
this is where roxanne comes in but
that's a long story
but it's a core girl means
uh uh king of the world carlo gilroy
right
chakravartan real emperor and
they want to have a son because that's
how they pass on the kingdom
so there's a lot of pressure in the old
times
on a king to have a son
now if you suddenly get bodhichitta
then the buddhas are celebrating because
they had a son or a daughter okay they
finally got their son or daughter okay
to get means they get extremely happy
and they take you into the family y'all
say
here's the tibetan uh sam dayton
now there's a weird comment that i don't
like so much
and i i i don't know how you're gonna
feel about it
but when you're a teacher it's your
responsibility to teach everything in
the text okay
so here it comes uh someday young num
telena
what happens if you lose that motivation
after getting it
okay what can a bodhisattva
be demoted or kicked out of the family
i'd like to say no but he says if you
ever could lose
your body chitta chai changhi tilney put
you would be expelled from the mahayana
you'd be ex
we had that boo when we had that tim
recently
bupa get kicked out
it was some negative thing we hadn't
anyway
uh it's not really
possible after you've had the experience
of bodhichitta
to lose that bodhichitta there are
stories
of people who had bad days
there's stories of bodhisattvas who had
bad days
and maybe it crossed their mind that
okay this living you know the famous
story was it
somebody asked him for his eyeball and
he
reached in and took it out and gave it
to the person
and then they jumped on it and smashed
it and he and it and for a moment
he said okay there's one person i don't
want to say
you know and uh you know did he lose
buddy china no
he just had a bad day i mean somebody
took his eyeball out and smashed it
okay so bodhis zappas can have bad days
but they don't really lose buddhism
okay
[Music]
maybe you're a person who was able to
get
to a point where you could read other
people's minds
and by the way translators i know i'm
talking too fast
i'll try to slow down uh
here i go deep breath all right
uh jucho means you can fly in the sky
you can walk on water things like that
is a very interesting word in tibetan
means
long-term long-term benefit
zero zero benefit
okay to learn to read other people's
minds
uh you know occasionally
and to be able to fly in the sky once in
a while
in the long run zero benefit
okay
if you could get a rough
understanding of the outline
of the lam rim it would be infinitely
more useful
than flying in the sky or reading other
people's minds
things like that okay moonshine
[Music]
yeah three jewels right what's the coin
mean
it means rare right rare so he says look
it's rare
for someone to read other people's minds
on a regular basis
and to be able to fly in the sky or walk
on water
those are rare
[Music]
what's then tim do you remember din
didn't like cheating
john
[Music]
it's not very meaningful it doesn't mean
much
it's going it's clean what does that
mean
yeah it's rare i mean you can't see
people don't fly around diamond mountain
that often
ah but duncan didn't change but there's
not much
point to it okay it doesn't help anybody
much
okay all right mayan and
anyway he says very funny he's a very
brilliant teacher
pardo you're going to get that every
time you die
in the bible so what's the big deal
you know everybody picks that up every
time they die
you keep dying constantly you know for a
while you can walk through walls
and fly in the sky did it help you so
far
you know did it make your life better
that during the bardo you could you fly
to other planets that's how planets are
populated you know you can
you need bardo time to get to another uh
galaxy to get born there that's why
formless realm people don't have a
bottle because they just born where they
die
okay they don't have to get somewhere
so everyone gets special powers
every time you die then help you you
know
bodhichitta is a real power
okay all right
we've reached the third benefit uh
or the third amazing cool thing about
booty too what was the first thing you
guys
you become
[Music]
yeah you join a new family uh you
you're you're a girl say you're a
jinnah putra you're a daughter or son of
the buddhist
okay you get into a new family what's
the second cool thing
yeah you get a new title you know dr
geshe
mr buddhist or michael roach
but and it sounds kind of silly but
it feels really good if it's true
you know it feels really really good it
feels
better than almost anything okay all
right
third benefit uh
silken number say silky
it's a special word and as i've said
many times
i learned all my words from my teacher i
didn't have a dictionary
i mean i had some dictionaries i never
used them
if i had a new word i would just go ask
my teacher
and i remember uh i asked him what's
silky number mean
and he said uh he said well
you know i'll tell you sometime and then
he didn't let me watch television and i
didn't want to watch dominion
but he enjoyed watching television
because he would learn
english and then he had a bell
and anytime something came on tv that he
thought i should see
he would ring the bell you know and i
was supposed to run upstairs
fast and so he rang the bell
and i ran upstairs and i burst into his
room and
he said there's silky number on the tv
right now
and it was queen elizabeth standing with
five or six other ladies in a in a line
you know
and he says which one is queen elizabeth
and i said
that one and he said that's silky number
and i'm like what do you mean and he
says
you don't even have to know what she
looks like she has this
what do you call it presence you know
majestic present you know
and she outshines the other ladies
like they're all wearing expensive
clothes she doesn't have her crown on
but you can see she's different
and he says that's silky number so the
third
a cool thing about bodhichitta
is that if they put you in a lineup
right
uh in a line with a bunch of other
dharma practitioners
but you have bodhichitta people will say
that's
that's the bodhisattva that's the
bodhisattva they are
they are somehow they are shining
compared to the other people somehow
there
there have a a glow about them like they
outshine these other serious dharma
practitioners but that one is different
that one stands out okay silky number
all right
so you silky nimba all the other dharma
practitioners
it's not that you want to be
more glorious than other people but you
are
okay and uh it's beautiful
and and again the big point here is that
there are sincere
and very very advanced
people we call them the tentacle name
is listeners and self-made buddhists
that's the technical name
but what it means is great meditators
great practitioners great
kind people who help other people there
are
amazing people in the world but if you
have jumped planets and made a personal
commitment
to billions of living beings there's no
comparison
at all with all the nice people you ever
met
in your life there's there's no
comparison at all
and it's not a competition but
wouldn't you rather be the cool person
on a billion planets
that could help billions and billions of
people directly
that's the point okay it's a whole
different level
it's beautiful to help other people
you know it's beautiful to save the
lives of animals it's beautiful to
to serve uh charities and feed people
it's a beautiful thing it's a it's a
it's the reason we exist but then to do
it directly
for billions of people at the same time
is just a whole another level and we
should
hope for that we should try to get there
you can
you have the capacity you just don't
know okay it's good to run a charity
it's good to
to do things in your neighborhood
but if you could do it on billions of
planets at the same time
that that's sexy i don't know it's just
like amazing
beautiful and you can your mind has the
capacity
because of emptiness your mind has the
capacity you just have to
wake it up okay somebody
there's a sutra called uh
people translated as stocks nra which is
you know it actually refers to the house
surrounded by the jewel trees
which is a better translation so someday
you guys should learn that
godzilla they are comparing
uh gatso what's ghetto ocean norbu
so in tibet especially because it was a
landlocked country they had no access to
the ocean
to get to the ocean meant six months of
dangerous
travel so there are lots of myths about
the ocean
the ocean was like a mythological thing
for them
and they believed that all precious gems
came from the bottom of the ocean
because of coral coral was one of the
few gems that you could get into bed
because it came through the bay of
bengalism
so anyway there was a tradition that all
the great
jewels came from the bottom of the ocean
then he says chingbo
there's this glass trinket
that people bring from
i don't know iran or something they're
just glass they're not diamond they're
not sapphire they're just
trinkets i heard the manhattan was
bought with 24
of glass pieces of glass you know
so he said compare the glass trinkets
to gems that you get from the bottom of
the ocean
and that's the difference between
bodhichitta
and other emotions similar emotions okay
tom j's silky number
so it's silky number jewels that come
from the barley ocean
silky number glass trinkets okay
cheap glass trinkets plastic nowadays
you'd say plastic
in the same way a person who gets
bodhichitta
outshines every other kind of
spiritual practitioner on this planet
okay it doesn't matter
or every other kind of person who's
working to help other people
in charities or something like that just
the person
who has 20-minute experience of jumping
planets
and making the sacred connection with
each being there
if you compare them to all the
do-gooders
of this planet
those that that person's 20 minutes is
more valuable
infinitely no comparison okay and i have
a
picture here a sapphire ring okay
the sapphire is beautiful you know
i spent many years trying to buy good
sapphires uh
they're this one is probably
certainly from uh ancient india
and you the new sapphires come mostly
from australia they're cut in thailand
and they don't have this color this is
called a royal blue
and you can't find it anywhere nowadays
very difficult to find so that sapphire
is quite valuable maybe it's
i don't know two three thousand dollars
okay
uh but the diamond each diamond
is is cost more than the sapphire each
diamond
around the sapphire is more valuable be
it
much much more viable okay
that's so that's a comparison of uh
diamond against uh any other gemstone
there's no comparison
i mean uh 10 carats of diamonds could be
could be millions of dollars and then 10
carats of anything else is gonna be a
few hundred dollars okay
as a gemstone dealer okay all right
uh and that comes from a famous sutra
called the house of the dual truth
next paragraph champion number tarpe
done then there's a suture called the
the the liberation of maitreya which can
also mean the story of my trainer
this is a very famous comparison
of bodhisattvas to other
kind people in the universe okay other
nice people in the universe compare
bodhisattva
to other beautiful helpful
charitable people in the universe okay
then
you could compare it to the birth of a
of royalty in ancient india the birth of
royalty
so i have a royal sun here picture
his name is maitree this
is my new grandson i'm very proud of him
he's extremely handsome i i told
his mother noor that he's this
i said he's the next handsome around
in the world which is his father's name
so she sent me a picture of a
lady holding a sign that said who who
was sick to this stomach for six months
who carried these 50 pounds around
who you know who got their guts torn up
to have the kid
and now you tell me he looks like the
father
and so i have to say he's a beautiful
combination of syria and japan
and the point is
uh if if a child is born
into royalty in the day of his birth
he is far more important to the country
than even the wisest of the officials of
the government
okay in ancient times in ancient times
uh that child when he's
by the way my tree was three months old
yesterday uh
that he's he's already uh
much more valued by the people of the
realm
than the wisest of the government
officials okay just by virtue of
who he is that means once you have been
once you have had the experience
of traveling to a million billions of
planets
to make a commitment to each person
there
then you are already
silky nimba all of the nice people in
the world
all of the good practitioners good
meditators good yoga practitioners
kind kind people
even the first hour after you've got
bodhichitta
you are you surpassed all of them
by billions of times okay all right
and that's one of the examples used in
ancient
buddhist literature for a new
bodhisattva
okay who was just born they're already
more important than
nice people who've been nice their whole
life
all right kardin khadim
here it is okay that's available
kadden's name
uh kadding means garuda
bird very similar to the western idea of
a phoenix bird
magical mythical glorious
shining firebird here's a picture of a
phoenix by the way
so i grew up in phoenix so i i remember
asking my mom what's phoenix mean
and she said oh that's a special bird
that's
born out of fire and ashes
of before a new bird comes out of the
ashes of the old broom
and comes up in flame in in fire
khadengi number here silky number
as soon as a garuda or a phoenix bird
is born they are already
more glorious than all the birds on on
earth
compared one phoenix to
all the seagulls all the sparrows all
the other
robin's bluebirds there's no comparison
you know a phoenix bird is two miles
high
made of fire and then compare them to
all these little beep beep meet me
you know no comparison okay that's the
idea
uh even when that bird is first born
from the fire they outshine
all these other people all these other
persons
[Music]
it means like a freshman
in college les dambo means a neophyte a
beginner
a rookie okay yeah a rookie bodhisattva
is already more important than all the
nice people on this planet
okay for the for the universe in in the
whole
for the whole universe a person who just
got body cheddar for the first time
is more important to the welfare
of the universe than all the nice people
on this planet
who are doing good things for other
people okay
and you know
means that's not my opinion
[Music]
being who he is he wants to explain
why okay he he wants to explain
why he can't stand to not tell us
why he says sung means
look that's not my opinion the buddha
said that that's a lung
in lumerick
that's the scriptural authority and now
he gives the
logical backup okay okay listen it's not
my dear the buddha said it you don't
believe me still
i'll prove it to you logically you don't
need you don't need to believe the
buddhist scripture
i'll tell you logically why that
bodhisattva
is more important saksa
come on tim hundred dollars [__] son
yeah i'm taking good hundred dollars for
guessing
hundred dollars for buddha daughter
okay hundred dollars uh saktam means
uh because they have taken
personal responsibility for
every living being every living being
how many
countless no number there's no number
how can you love countless people it's a
mystery
you know how can you meet countless
people in 20 minutes
that's another mystery because
you never get to the last one and the 20
minutes is up
but it happens it works you can do it
you do do it
that's what happens in the direct
experience of bodhichitta you
you meet people who have no number
and you lock some what's that
i'll take care of you each one
you you spend a few minutes with each
one
to explain to them why you're going to
take responsibility for them mr wu was
talking about
uh calling mom and
you know why does mom keep sending you
money i have no idea
but they decide they the body suffer
in 20 minutes makes that commitment
to countless living beings who are
infinite
in number somehow the bodhisattva gets
to the last one
where there is no last one okay
it's amazing it's a miracle okay
yay all right so i guess that karma
might be pretty strong
they should do doj
now he starts to talk about let's look
at the next picture
okay this is diamonds you know
i i have trouble finding pictures i'm
having trouble
finding good pictures of
doj segment for a hundred dollars
dang who said it first
okay 33 bucks each okay
very very important buddhist term
sliver of diamond sliver of diamond okay
as you take
as i've said many times you you can't
cut a diamond with anything in the
universe
you can't scratch a diamond with
anything in the universe except another
diamond
but you can smash in time that's a
different thing
with a hammer and and you'll get many
torches
slivers of diamond okay so now
pabonko rinpoche takes the conversation
and by the way shanti deva
takes the master shantidev it takes the
conversation to
slivers of diamond okay so let's say you
had a diamond
and you hit it with a hammer and now you
have pieces of diamond door jig
chuck means break it okay you can smash
it diamond
young men but
that doesn't mean you can't call it a
diamond anymore
the pieces you can smash a diamond
into many pieces but each
piece retains the name of diamond
ming mindor means it doesn't lose its
identity
it's still diamond you can smash a
diamond
but those pieces are still pure diamond
and you know the the importance of that
what is the importance of how do we
explain it in the diamond cutter when we
explain the name of the diamond cutter
sutra
we talk about the power of each piece of
environment
yeah everything in this room has its own
emptiness there are billions of
emptinesses in this room
i like to say the last hair on your
eyebrow
also has its own emptiness okay yeah
uh i was teaching that so long my
eyebrows got number
uh so anyway uh each piece
is still diamond okay dorna then he goes
off onto a famous
explanation of what those
pieces can do for you okay and at first
he says
each piece of each piece sliver
of diamond silky noon
what's that outshines
ser gold yeah okay
and here's the next picture i think
there's a picture
yeah so i was in the jewelry business
for 19 years
it was my job to find the diamonds and
then they sent them to a factory
they put the gold ring they put them in
the gold ring
and we didn't even have a special
department for buying gold
it was just a commodity you you go to
another bank
they sell gold you buy bars of gold you
bring it home
there's no special thing about gold
okay the gold in this ring is worth
about twenty dollars
uh the diamond is worth could be worth
twenty thousand dollars
you see what i mean so silky okay
the diamond silky nun
the gold okay the is the gold precious
is it good to be a nice person in this
world
is it good to have a charity or is it
good to
feed people is it good to even be
an advanced meditator uh
and is it good to have overcome your
negativities to a great extent yeah it's
like
gold it's extremely beautiful and
valuable
but compared to the diamond is it
doesn't really
there's no comparison it doesn't mean
it's unimportant the gold it doesn't
mean gold is unimportant
it means gold is beautiful gold is
extremely
attractive but compared to the diamond
is nothing
okay and they go together okay
that's a big point okay how do you get
to the diamond
you go to the goal okay gold here
represents great meditation ability
[Music]
serving other people day to day
and then suddenly you graduate to
buddhist
bodhichitta you get to the diamond okay
all right um uh
uh lula means uh brokenness
the condition of being broke like you
were in uh
i don't know about you in my 20s i was
i was very good at um i
was me and veronica we often say we were
lucky because we grew up quite poor
we grew up in big families with no money
and that's um poverty
relative diamond still removes
poverty even if you have a piece of a
diamond
it still removes your poverty that's
going to be a metaphor
for something else and we're getting
there don't worry okay
and uh
bodhichitta is the same now let's see
what the metaphor stands for we have
about five minutes left
in the class yeah right tim we have time
to explain the metaphor right
all right next paragraph girl seiki
lomi nukian even if you are incapable
of practicing the six perfections
okay even if you you haven't got to the
six perfections yet
which are giving
ethical life not getting
angry
having fun doing good stuff
meditation and wisdom even if you
haven't got there yet
at all okay love me like
it's too much for you i can't do that
yet yuki is simply too
but if you have that intention
that motivation to jump many planets and
help countless people
yahweh say
[Music]
we still call you a bodhisattva okay
it's like smashing the diamond
each piece is still a diamond a
defective bodhisattva
is still a bodhisattva uh an incompetent
bodhisattva
is still a buddhism
even a honeycomb incompetent
bodhisattva anything an incompetent
bodhisattva does
is still greater than any good deed
done by anyone else in the world
okay any small good thing a bodhisattva
does
silky numbers every good thing
that could be done by anyone else in the
world okay pretty radical statement
choke the gear he says infinitely more
benefit okay
even those great listeners and self-made
buddhists meaning
great meditators deep insight into
emptiness
but still they are the diamond compared
to the gold
okay kodave cell
and finally the buddha himself said
that if you get this diamond you can
remove the poverty of quran
of the whole centaur the whole suffering
universe
you can remove their poverty if you have
this diamond
okay and and again uh
he says incompetent bodhisattva
okay cannot do anything right just
having buddy tuna is more valuable
than than what everyone else is all the
nice things that other people are doing
it's more valuable okay all right so
we'll continue that uh tomorrow
i wanted to say you know this always
comes up it's always my job to talk
about
it uh today we offered the class for
free everyone was welcome to come for
free
my teacher gave all his teachings for
he never charged anybody for
i don't know 60 years that he taught
he never charged anybody once and then
people asked me you know why why we have
to pay for this loan room
do we have to pay for the salary and
first of all you don't have to pay
if you'd like to take the rest of the
course for free
you can click on a link here and
you can take the main course for free
and you don't have to pay anything
there's also a link for paying for the
course
and that money doesn't go nobody gets
rich nobody has a
you know huge house made of gold or
diamond
and uh you know
it's just that when i take an airplane
and yesterday we drove here
to diamond mountain it was how much six
hour driving
and we stopped and we have to fill up
the
gas in the car and i went to the gas
station guy
in pace in arizona i said i'm teaching
bloody china tomorrow
do i have to pay for the gas he's like
huh
he said yeah you do have to pay for the
gas and get them
out of the you know i'm okay okay you
know
so listen i'm sorry it's just things we
have to pay for
you know there's electricity people have
to travel here we have to
pau and pachi keep eating i don't know
what's wrong
uh there's just some stuff we can't get
for free
uh because the whole world's not
buddhist yet so uh
so i personally i'd like to say i really
appreciate
when you do help pay for things it helps
us a lot
you know we have to pay for the gas we
have to pay for food
we can't get here otherwise i have a
computer it's expensive i need it
and so so you're very welcome to take
the course for free
if the guy would give us the gaps for
free i'd be happy to give you the course
for free
you could still have the course for free
if you really want the course for free
but i think it's cool and i think it's
responsible and
to help pay for stuff it's just i've
learned in my life my long life
that when you help pay for things you
feel better
and and it's more honest okay so
you know but if you really don't want to
that's fine
and you're welcome to come for free and
i'll i'll always give you that option
we'll always give you that option but
it's hard for us it makes things hard
for us so everybody chips in a little
bit it's helpful
okay all right i'll see you tomorrow uh
for the next
uh story about buddy timmy
and i don't know i'm telling you if
if you don't do anything else in your
whole life
if you can have 20 minutes of real body
jenna
then then you then you lived a real life
and your life had
had meaning then your your life had
meaning
and i and i tell you that from my
personal life
your your whole life is worth something
if you can have 20 minutes of real
bullies okay
all right see you tomorrow
[Music]